export const easy = [
  {
    question: "If all apples are fruits and all fruits are food, then all apples are:",
    options: ["Vegetables", "Food", "Seeds", "None"],
    answer: "Food"
  },
  {
    question: "Find the odd one out: 2, 4, 6, 9, 8",
    options: ["4", "6", "9", "8"],
    answer: "9"
  },
  {
    question: "If A = 1, B = 2, C = 3, then what is the value of CAB?",
    options: ["312", "324", "3121", "None"],
    answer: "312"
  },
  {
    question: "Which number comes next: 5, 10, 20, 40, ?",
    options: ["45", "50", "60", "80"],
    answer: "80"
  },
  {
    question: "If 3 + 2 = 13, 4 + 3 = 25, 5 + 4 = ?",
    options: ["36", "30", "45", "40"],
    answer: "41"
  }
];

export const medium = [
  {
    question: "John is taller than Sam. Sam is taller than Paul. Who is the shortest?",
    options: ["John", "Sam", "Paul", "Can't Say"],
    answer: "Paul"
  },
  {
    question: "Which number completes the series: 3, 6, 11, 18, ?",
    options: ["25", "26", "27", "28"],
    answer: "27"
  },
  {
    question: "If in a code, DOG = 4157, CAT = 3120, then BAT = ?",
    options: ["2120", "3120", "2122", "4120"],
    answer: "2120"
  },
  {
    question: "Select the odd one: Pen, Pencil, Eraser, Paper, Chalk",
    options: ["Pencil", "Eraser", "Paper", "Chalk"],
    answer: "Paper"
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the correct analogy: Book : Reading :: Fork : ?",
    options: ["Drawing", "Writing", "Stirring", "Eating"],
    answer: "Eating"
  }
];

export const hard = [
  {
    question: "If Monday is the 1st day, what day is the 50th day?",
    options: ["Monday", "Thursday", "Saturday", "Sunday"],
    answer: "Saturday"
  },
  {
    question: "A clock shows 3:15. What is the angle between the hour and the minute hand?",
    options: ["0°", "7.5°", "30°", "45°"],
    answer: "7.5°"
  },
  {
    question: "If TRAIN = 8125914, then RAIN = ?",
    options: ["125914", "825914", "12914", "8914"],
    answer: "125914"
  },
  {
    question: "Which number should replace the question mark? 4, 9, 16, 25, ?",
    options: ["30", "34", "36", "49"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the mirror image of ‘L’?",
    options: ["ᒧ", "ᒪ", "L", "None"],
    answer: "ᒧ"
  }
];
